<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="savings">You save:</string>
    <string name="shoeEightFemaleDescriptionLong">This item enhances your autumn wardrobe to the finest! Elegant ballerina of the trend brand Another A made of suede in blue with Lyra perforation and tassels on the sheet.</string>
    <string name="avbSize">Available sizes:</string>
    <string name="btnService">Service Call</string>
    <string name="shoeEightFemaleList">• pleasantly soft inner lining "\n"• feminine or elegantly styled - a true sight "\n"• slip-resistant running sole</string>
    <string name="shoeFiveFemaleDescriptionLong">This cool model from Gabor is the perfect companion for warm summertime. The soft nubuck leather is lightly gathered on the instep and is thus particularly fashionable.</string>
    <string name="shoeFiveFemaleList">• soft padded insole "\n"• closes in the heel with a small buckle "\n"• anti-slip synthetic sole with a moderate heel height</string>
    <string name="shoeFourFemaleDescriptionLong">The \"Run Ultra\" by Nike from Flywire fibers in silver for a supportive and individual fit, is ideally suited as a sports shoe - and is, of course, also top in terms of style.</string>
    <string name="shoeFourFemaleList">• sock-like entrance "\n"• elastic heel area with support strap "\n"• waffle outer sole for traction</string>
    <string name="shoeNineFemaleDescriptionLong">Marc O\'Polo combines skillful sporting elements with feminine chic. From a light gray suede with logo details, the sneaker can be combined with jeans or dress.</string>
    <string name="shoeNineFemaleList">• softly padded upper edge "\n"• great combination partner for sportive looks \"• • flexible outsole with anti-slip profile</string>
    <string name="shoeOneFemaleDescriptionLong">This fashionable sandal from Apple of Eden, made of soft suede leather in a vintage look, gives summer outfits a stylish finish. Soft leather straps provide support.</string>
    <string name="shoeOneFemaleList">• wonderfully soft inner lining made from leather \"• • particularly nice to airy dresses and skirts\" \"• Contrasts sole with strong profile</string>
    <string name="shoeSevenFemaleDescriptionLong">The solid version of the classic sneaker from Converse comes here from a light canvas in gold. In metallic look, it becomes a new favorite of the season with a striking finish.</string>
    <string name="shoeSevenFemaleList">• pleasantly soft inner lining \"• makes any outfit a fashion hit\" • • striking running sole in white</string>
    <string name="shoeSixFemaleDescriptionLong">The ballerinas of Buffalo with favorite potential! It comes in a light version and is inspired by puristic black with striking rhinestones.</string>
    <string name="shoeSixFemaleList">• pleasantly soft inner lining "\n"• great combination partner to many looks "\n"• slip-resistant running sole</string>
    <string name="shoeThreeFemaleDescriptionLong">This stylish model comes from the house of Ludwig Görtz and will complete your wardrobe stylishly. The fine smooth leather in black fascinates with casual buckle detail.</string>
    <string name="shoeThreeFemaleList">• complete full leather interior "\n"• for ladies who love it ever so noble and, as it were, casual "\n"• anti-slip rubber outsole with profile</string>
    <string name="shoeTwoFemaleDescriptionLong">Dress with the comfortable pumps by Paul Green. The heel has a comfortable everyday and office height, the velvety leather in black is soft and cuddly.</string>
    <string name="shoeTwoFemaleList">• highest wearing comfort due to leather interior "\n"• leather-related block heel "\n"• light TPU rubber sole</string>
    <string name="shoeZeroFemaleDescriptionLong">Ultimate comeback of the sneaker icon STAN SMITH from Adidas Originals. Already sold in the seventies millionfold, he triumphs today as a must-have of all Fashionistas.</string>
    <string name="shoeZeroFemaleList">• Anti-bacterial OrthoLite® equipment "\n"• Characteristic features "\n"• Rubber sole with grippy profile for good grip</string>
</resources>